Guide to the Harper & Row, Publishers Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series X: Photographs
  - Davidson, Bill
  - Davidson, Irwin D.
  - Davidson, Lionel
  - Davis, Chester
  - Davis, Christopher
  - Davis, H.L.
  - Davis, Joseph
  - Davis, Wesley Ford
  - Davidson, Edward
  - Dayan, General Moshe
  - Deakin, F.W.
  - De Beus, J.G.
  - DeBrodt, Barbara Ream
  - De Chair, Somerset
  - De Chant, John A.
  - Decker, Sunny
  - De Ford, Sara (Box 315)
  - Degler, Carl
  - De Hartog, Jan
  - De Hirsch, Katrina
  - Deighton, Len
  - David, De Jong
  - Delafield, E.M.
  - Deland, Margaret
  - Delderfield R.F.
  - Delgado, Jose M.R.
  - Delpech, Bertrand Poirot
  - De Matteo, Sebastian
  - De Mendelssohn, Peter
  - De Riencourt, Amaury
  - Dominique, D'ermo
  - Dessart, Gina
  - Dewitt, William A.
  - Dickens, Monica
  - Dickinson, Peter
  - Dick-Read, Grantly, M.D.
  - Dillie, John
  - Dinneen, Joseph
  - Dixon, Vernor
  - Doctor X
  - Dohrman, Richard
  - Doig, Desmond
  - Dolman, John Jr.
  - Donovan, Zober
  - Dorcus And DaSilva
  - Dorian, Frederick
  - Douglas, Marjorie Stoneman
  - Douglas, William
  - Douglass, Donald
  - Dreikus, Rudolf M.D.
  - Minoh Drouet P.
  - Droke, Maxwell
  - Drucker, Peter F. (Box 316)
  - Drury, Aubrey
  - Dryer, Bernard Victor
  - Dublin, Dr. Louis
  - Dubois W.E.B.
  - Duchanmes, Jacques
  - Duff, Dr. R. S.
  - Dufour, Charles L.
  - Dugan, James
  - Dulles, Allen
  - Dulles, Foster Rhea
  - Dunbar, Janet
  - Duncan, david Douglas
  - Duncan, Dorothy
  - Dunlap, Orrin E.
  - Dunlap, Hasel Peckinpaugh
  - Dunn, Dorothy
  - Dunn, Katherine
  - Dunphy, Jack
  - Flint, Dupre
  - Dupuy, Ernest, & Dupuy, Trevor
  - Durrenmatt, Friedrich
  - Dusenbury, G.
  - Dyer, John P.
  - Dyer, Murray
  - Eastlake, Wm.
  - Eaton, Clement
  - Eastman, Max
  - Eaton, Evelyn
  - Eckstein, Gustav
  - Eclov, Shirley (Box 317)
  - Edwards, Phil
  - Egan, Lesley
  - Ehrlich, Max
  - Ehrlich, Bettina
  - Eggler, Albert
  - Eiby, G. A.
  - Eichelberger, Clark M.
  - Elliot, 3rd, E.E.
  - Elliot, Elisabeth
  - Elliot, George P.
  - Elliot, H.C.
  - Elliot, Osborn
  - Elliot, Sumner Locke
  - Embrie, Edwin R.
  - Emmett, J. A.
  - Engler, Richard Ed, Jr.
  - Engstrand, David
  - Enthoven, Dr. Alain C.
  - Ernst, Morris L.
  - Ertz, Susan
  - Espy, Willard R.
  - Esquire (Birmingham) & (Charmante)
  - Eudy, Mary
  - Eurich, Alvin C.
  - Eustis, Helen
  - Evan, Carol
  - Evanoff, Vlad
  - Evan Evans
  - Evans, John W.
  - Ewing, David W.
  - Exley
  - Exman, Eugene
  - Fadiman, Clifton
  - Fair, Ronald L.
  - Fall, Thomas
  - Faltermayer, Edmund K.
  - Farley, Mowat
  - Farmer, Lawrence
  - Farnham, Dwight
  - Farnham, Marynia
  - Farrell, J. G.
  - Faulkner, Harold U.
  - Farce, Paovl
  - Faure, Elie
  - Fay, Jr. Paul B.
  - Fearn, Dr.
  - Feinberg, Samuel M.
  - Feinburch, Wilfred
  - Fellows, Alice
  - Fenwick, Elizabeth P.
  - Ferguson, Donita (Box 318)
  - Fermor, Patrick Leigh
  - Ferraro, Norma Downey
  - Ferril, Thomas Hornsby
  - Fitchter, George St.
  - Fiddle, Seymour
  - Filer, Tom
  - Filier, Louis
  - Findley, Francine
  - Fineberg, Solomon A.
  - Finch, Edith
  - Fineman, Irving
  - Finletter, Gretchen
  - Finletter, Thomas K.
  - Finn, Rev. Wm. J.
  - Finocchiaro, Mary
  - Firth, Anthony
  - Fischer, David H.
  - Fischer, Louis
  - Fischer, Markoosha
  - Fischer, Dorothy Canfield
  - Fischer, F. Hope
  - Fischer, John
  - Fischer, Robert Moore
  - Fischer, Roger
  - Fischer, Vardis
  - Fishwick, Marshall W.
  - Fitch & Rockwell
  - Fitt, Mary
  - Fitshenry, Robert I.
  - Flaccus, Kimball
  - Flanner, Janet
  - Flavin, Martin
  - Fleming, Peier
  - Flexner, James Thomas
  - Foner, Eric
  - Foot, Sir Hugh
  - Footner, Hulbert
  - Forbis, William H.
  - Ford, Dr. C. S.
  - Ford, Henry
  - Forrunners to Everest
  - Forman, Henry James (Box 319)
  - Foster, Elizabeth
  - Foster, James R.
  - Fox, Larry
  - Frady, Marshall
  - France, Anatole
  - Francis, Dick
  - Frank, Jerome
  - Frankau, Pamela
  - Frankel, Charles
  - Franken, Rose
  - Frederickson, George
  - Freedman, Nancy & Benedict
  - Freehling, Nicolas
  - Freehling, William W.
  - Freeman, Larry
  - Freeman, Lucy
  - Fremon, Suzanne, Strait
  - Freydbert, Margaret
  - Friedman, Edward L.
  - Friedrich, Carl J.
  - Fromm, Belia
  - Fromm, Erich
  - Fuller, Blair
  - Fuller, Edmond
  - Fuller, Major J. F. C.
  - Funk, Charles Earle Jr.
  - Furnas, J. C.
  - Fornns, Manthedith
  - Futagawa, Yukio and Itoh, Teiji The Essential Japanese House
  - Futagawa, Yukio
  - Gaddis, Paul
  - Gallie, Menna
  - Gallo, Max
  - Gallup, Dick
  - Gallup, George
  - Galton, Lawrence
  - Gammon, Roland
  - Garbo, Norman and Goodkind, Howard
  - Gardner, John
  - Garland, Hamlin
  - Garraty, John
  - Garrison, Roger
  - Garve, Andrew
  - Gary, Romain
  - Gascoigne, Bamber & Christina
  - Gaskin, Catherine
  - Gates, Charles M. & Johansen, Dorothy O.
  - Gavin, General
  - Geelmuyden, Hans
  - Geer, Andrew (Box 320)
  - Gelb, Arthur & Barbara
  - Gehman, Richard
  - Geld, Ellen Bromfield
  - Gesell, Coates, Austin
  - Gesell
  - Gibb & Knowlton
  - Gibney, Frank
  - Gibson, Charles
  - Gies, Joseph
  - Gilb, Corrinne
  - Gilbert, B. Bentley
  - Gilbert, Michael
  - Gillespie, Clyde
  - Gillies, Mary Davis
  - Gipson, Fried
  - Gipson, Lawrence H.
  - Gitlin, Todd
  - Glasser, Dr. William
  - Gleason, S. Everett
  - Glenn, Edmund S. (Saxxen Fellowship)
  - Glubb P. John B.
  - Goldberg, Arthur
  - Goldfarb, Ronald
  - Goldkwopf, David
  - Goldman, Vera
  - Gollancz, Victor
  - Goodfield, June
  - Good Housekeeping
  - Goodwin, John
  - Gordon, Fred
  - Gottfried, Sue D.
  - Gould, Franklin F
  - Goulding, Phil
  - Graham, Frank Jr.
  - Graham, John Alexander
  - Graham, Phyllis
  - Grant, Joan
  - Gray, George W.
  - Grant, Joan
  - Green, Anne
  - Green, Julian
  - Green, Martin (Box 321)
  - Green, Paul
  - Greenbaum, Leonard
  - Greenbank, Tony
  - Greenberg, Saul N. & Joan R.
  - Greenberg, David
  - Greenberg, David Mrs.
  - Greene, Margaret C. L.
  - Greenman, Frances Cranmer
  - Greenough, Ruth Hornblower
  - Gregory, Dick (original)
  - Grendley, Janet Gillespie
  - Grey, Zane
  - Griffith, Thomas
  - Grimm, William C.
  - Grisman, Aronold P.
  - Gropius, Walter
  - Grossbach, Robert
  - Grosscup, Lee
  - Groth, John
  - Grottrup, Irmgarp
  - Grover, Linda
  - Groves, Gen. L. H.
  - Grub, Davis
  - Gruenbert, Sidonie Matsner
  - Genther, John
  - Guess, William Francis
  - Guild, Warren Redwood, MD
  - Gunther, John
  - Guttridge, Len and Smith, Jay D.
  - Haan, Aubrey (Box 322)
  - Haas, Emmy
  - Hadas, Moses
  - Hagen, Clifford
  - Haich, Elizabeth
  - Halacy, D. S. Jr.
  - Hale, Oron J.
  - Hall, Donald
  - Hall, James Baker
  - Hall, Leoward DP
  - Hall, Thomas Wesley
  - Halle, Louis J.
  - Halliday, E. M.
  - Halper, Albert
  - Hamilton, Hamish
  - Hamarskjold, Dag
  - Hampshire, Stuart
  - Handel, Paul W.
  - Hanley, Gerald
  - Hanlon, Harvey
  - Hansen, Harry
  - Hansen, Thorkild
  - Hardy, Lindsay
  - Hardy, Thomas
  - Harlow, William M.
  - Harper's Magazine
  - Harrington, Evans
  - Harris, J. N.
  - Harris, Seantor Fred R.
  - Harris, Seymour E.
  - Harris, Dr. Thomas A.
  - Harrison, William
  - Harss, Luis
  - Hartman, Lee Foster
  - Hatfield, Senator Mark O.
  - Haugland, Vern
  - Havighurst, Walter
  - Hawes, Bess Lomax
  - Hawkings, Gerard
  - Hay, John
  - Hayakowa, S. I.
  - Hayes, Alfred
  - Hayter, Adrian
  - Hazard, John W.
  - Hazel, Robert Elvin
  - Healey, Ben
  - Heard, Gerald
  - Heath, Robert W.
  - Heath, W. L.
  - Hecht, Ben
  - Heiby, Walter A.
  - Heilbrower, Robert L.
  - Heinz P., W. C.
  - Heisenberg, Werner
  - Helander, Gunnar
  - Helitzer, Florence
  - Helm, Mackinley
  - Hempstone, Smith
  - Herbert, Don
  - Herdman, Ramona
  - Heren, Louis
  - Heren, Louis
  - Herhaus, Ernst (Box 323)
  - Hermanovski, Egils & family
  - Herrmann, Paul
  - Herzog, Arthur
  - Hess, Stephen
  - Heydenwich, Ludwig
  - Heymann, Frederick G.
  - Hicks, John D.
  - Higgins, Marguerite
  - Highsmith, Patricia P.
  - Hill, Patti
  - Hill, Ralph Nading
  - Hill, Roger
  - Hill, Russell
  - Hinckley, Helen
  - Hinton, Harold B.
  - Hites, Maynard B.
  - Hoagland, Kathleen
  - Hoffer, Eric
  - Hoffman, Paul G.
  - Hoffnung, Gerard
  - Hogrefe, Pearl
  - Holden, Anne
  - Hollingshead
  - Hollis, Jim
  - Holmes, John
  - Holmes, Marian S.
  - Holzman, Robert S.
  - Honour, Hugh
  - Hopkins, Harry L.
  - Hopkins, Stanley
  - Howard, Elizabeth Jane
  - Howe, Helen
  - Howe, Henry F.
  - Howells, William Dean
  - Hoyne, Henry
  - Hoyle, Fred
  - Hubbell, Jay B. Dr.
  - Huber, Richard M.
  - Hubert, Dreyfus (original)
  - Hughes, Emmet John
  - Hughes, H. Stuart
  - Hughes, Ted B.
  - Hunt, George P.
  - Hunt, Morton
  - Hunter, J. A.
  - Huot, Louis C. (Box 324)
  - Hurd, Charles
  - Hurst, Fanny
  - Hutchison, Collister
  - Hutchison, R. C.
  - Huxley, Aldous
  - Huxley, Julian
  - Huxley, Juliette
  - Hyman, Harold M.
  - Illich, Ivan
  - Institute for Sex Research
  - Isaac, Rael Jean
  - Jacobs, Harvey
  - Jaeger, Henry
  - Jameson, Storm
  - Janeway, Elizabeth
  - Jastrow, Robert
  - Jay, Charlotte P.
  - Jenkins, Herbert
  - Jennison, Keith W.
  - Joaquin, Nick
  - Jobe, Joseph
  - Johnson, Emil R.
  - Johnson, E. W.
  - Johnson, Gerald
  - Johnson, June
  - Johnson, Sally Patrick
  - Jones, Candy
  - Jones, Dorothea
  - Jones, Gordon
  - Jones, Howard P.
  - Jones, Kenneth L.
  - Josselyn, Irene M. D.
  - Jovanovitch, William
  - Joyce, Walter
  - Kahn, Joan
  - Kahn, Roger (original) (Box 325)
  - Kahn & Sayers
  - Kalashnikoff, Nicholas
  - Kaltenbach, John E.
  - Kaminsky, Max
  - Kaplan, Harold J.
  - Kaplan, Philip
  - Kaplan, Fred L.
  - Katcher, Leo
  - Kates, George N.
  - Katkov, George
  - Kauffmann, Stanley
  - Kaufmann, William W.
  - Kaye-Smith, Sheila
  - Kearns, William H. Jr.
  - Keating & Carter
  - Kelland, Clarence
  - Kelsey, Vera
  - Kendall, Carol
  - Kennaway, James S.
  - Kennerly, Byron
  - Keon, Michael
  - Keppel, Francis
  - Kessler, Jascha
  - Kesten, Hermann
  - Keyes, Frances Parkinson
  - King, Louise Tate
  - King, Dr. Martin Luther
  - Kinmont, Jill
  - Kintner, William R.
  - Kirst, Hans Hellmut
  - Kittler, Glen D.
  - Klein, William Karl
  - Kluger, Richard
  - Knebel & Bailey
  - Knebel, Fletcher
  - Knight, Damon
  - Knowlton, Robert
  - Koch, Stephen
  - Kohler, Dayton
  - Kohler, Foy D.
  - Kohlmeter, Jr. Louis M.
  - Kohn, Hans
  - Kouwenhoven, John A.
  - Kraft, Joseph
  - Krasner, William
  - Kriuitskyi, W. G.
  - Krythe, Maymie
  - Kuh, Katharine
  - Kuhlman, Wilson
  - Kumin, Maxine
  - Kuroki, Ben (Box 326)
  - Labedz, Leopold
  - Lach, Alma
  - LaFollette, Suzanne
  - Laird, Jean E.
  - Lall, Arthur S.
  - Lamb, Dana & Virginia
  - Lamont, Thomas W.
  - Land, Myrick
  - Langer, William L.
  - Langton, Jane
  - Lanning, George
  - Lansdale, Edward Maj. Gen.
  - Lape, Fred
  - Lapp, Ralph
  - Larrouse, Pix
  - Larson, Arthur
  - Lasagna, Louis
  - Lattimore, Richmond
  - Laumer, Keith
  - Lavender, David
  - Laver, James
  - Lawner, Lynne
  - Laxalt, Robert
  - Lease, Ruth & Siks
  - Lebeson, Anita Libman
  - Leckie, Robert
  - Lee, Asher
  - Lee, Gypsy
  - Lee, Irving
  - Lee, Jim
  - Leech, Margaret
  - Leggett, John
  - Leigh, James
  - Leiper, G. B. (Saxton Fellowship)
  - Lemay, Harding (Box 327)
  - Leonard, Charles
  - Leonard, Frank
  - Leonard, Mosley
  - Lermala, Elizabeth
  - Leterman, Elmer G.
  - Leuchtenburg, William, E.
  - Levart, Herbert
  - Levi-Strauss, Claude
  - Levier, Tony
  - Letton, Jennette & Francis
  - Lewinsohn, Richard
  - Levinson, Harry F.
  - Levitt, Saul
  - Lewis, Ralph F.
  - Lewis, W. Arthur
  - Lichtner, Marvin
  - Lightfoot, Gordon
  - Lilienthal, David E.
  - Lincoln, Dr. Miriam
  - Lindop, Audrey
  - Lindey, Alexander
  - Lindsay, R. B.
  - Link, Arthur S.
  - Linkletter, Monte
  - Linton, Calvin D.
  - Lippimann, Walter
  - Lipton, Lawrence
  - Lipset, Seymour Martin
  - Lloyd, A. E.
  - Lobell, Nathan D.
  - Lobsenz, Herbert
  - Lodge, Henry, Cabot
  - Lolos, Kimon
  - Lomax, Louis
  - London, Dr. Perry
  - Long, Dwight
  - Longrigg, Roger
  - Lorant, Stefan
  - Lord, Walter
  - Loth, David (Box 328)
  - Longhlin, David
  - Loughlin, John
  - Lounsbery, Elizabeth
  - Love, Edmund G.
  - Lovell, A. C. B.
  - Loveridge, Arthur
  - Lowdenmilk, Walten Clay
  - Lubell, Samuel
  - Lukacs, John
  - Lukas, J. Anthony
  - Lundberg, Ferdinand
  - Luria, Jack (Saxton)
  - Lyford, Joseph
  - Lynes, Russell
  - Lyon, Dana P.
  - Lyons, Eugene
  - Lyttleton OP., Raymond
  - McAdoo, Richard B.
  - McCoy, John Pleasant
  - McCabe, Charles R.
  - McCune, Wesley
  - McDermott, Geoffrey
  - McFee, William
  - McGrane, Dr. Reginald C.
  - McLoed, A. S.
  - McMullen, Mary
  - McMurry, George H.
  - McSorley, Edmond
  - Maass, Joachim
  - MacAdams, Lewis
  - MacCracken, Noble, Dr.
  - MacDougal, Alan Ross
  - MacGregor, Frank S.
  - Maciver, Robert
  - Maclean, Fitznoy
  - MacLeish, Roderick
  - MacMillan, Harold (Box 329)
  - MacNeil, Robert
  - MacRidis, Roy C.
  - MacSorley, Don
  - Macy, John W., Jr.
  - Maddock, Alison
  - Maddux, Rachel
  - Magill, Frank
  - Mahoney, Thomas
  - Malik, Charles
  - Maling, Arthur
  - Malkin, Robert J.
  - Manashaw, Donald
  - Manchester, William
  - Maney, Dick P.
  - ManKiewitz, Don
  - Mannix, Dan
  - Manry, Robert
  - Marcham, F. G.
  - Marek, George R.
  - Marion, Francis
  - Maritain, Jacques
  - Mark, Vernon
  - Markel, Lester
  - Marrow, Alfred J.
  - Marsh, Sir Edward
  - Marsh, Willard
  - Marshall, Jack
  - Marshall, Smelser
  - Martini, Helen
  - Martin, John Bartlow
  - Martin, Ralph
  - Martin, Sylvia
  - Marthe, Margaret S.
  - Marton, Gregory
  - Marugg, Jim
  - Marx, Arthur P.
  - Marx, Graucho
  - Marzollo, Jean Martin
  - Masson, Georgina
  - Masaryk, Jan
  - Maslow, Abraham H.
  - Masters, John (Box 330)
  - Mather, Melissa
  - Matsuoka, Yoko
  - Mattheissen, Peter
  - Maugham, Lord Robin
  - Maule, Frances P.
  - Maurois, Andre
  - Maurois, Gerald
  - Maxfield, Henry P.
  - Maxwell, William
  - Maxwell, Gavin
  - Mayer, Martin
  - Mayeroff, Milton
  - Mazo, Earl
  - McCormick, Robert C.
  - McCoy, Alfred W.-Cathleen R.
  - Mcginnis, Ralph J.
  - Mckenna, Richard
  - McKenney, Ruth
  - McLuhan, Marshall
  - McMurtry, Larry
  - McNamars, Robert S.
  - McNulty, Nancy G.
  - Mehta, Ved
  - Meigs, James
  - Melbin, Murray
  - Mellers, Wilfred
  - Mensendieck, Bess
  - Meray, Tibor
  - Meredith, Scott
  - Meyer, Edith Patterson
  - Meynell, Lawrence
  - Meyneng, Meyette
  - Michel, Henri
  - Milford, Nancy
  - Mitford, Nancy (Box 331)
  - Milhollen, Hirst D.
  - Millay, Edna St. Vincent
  - Miller, John C.
  - Miller, Nolan
  - Miller, Thomas
  - Milne, Lorus & Margery
  - Milne, Charles S.
  - Miscellaneous
  - Mitchell, Ronald
  - Mlakar, Frank
  - Moholy, Nagy
  - Molenaro, Ursula
  - Moley, Reymond
  - Malnar, Maria
  - Momaday, Scott
  - Montgomery, Dorothy Ford
  - Montgomery, Marion H.
  - Montross, Lynn
  - Moore, Byron
  - Moore, Gilbert
  - Moore, Msgr
  - Morehouse, Laurence e.
  - Morgan, Charles
  - Morgan, J. Pierpoint
  - Mongenthau, Henry Jr.
  - Morley, F. V.
  - Monnis, I. V.
  - Morris, Joe Alex
  - Morris, Everett
  - Morris, Richard B.
  - Morris, William P.
  - Morris, William & Mary
  - Morris, William
  - Morris, Willie
  - Morton, George
  - Morton, Louis
  - Morton, Stella
  - Moseley, George
  - Moses, Grandma
  - Mosley, Leonard (Box 332)
  - Mouni, Sadhu
  - Mowat, Farley
  - Mowry, George E.
  - Moyers, Bill
  - Mulac, Margaret E.
  - Muller-Alfeld, P.
  - Munday, Albert H.
  - Murphy, Gardner
  - Murphy, Grace E.
  - Murray, Pauli
  - Murphy, Paul l.
  - Murray, Paul
  - Mydans, Carl
  - Myrdal, Gunvar
  - Nabokov, Vladimir
  - Najafi, Najmeh
  - Namier, L. B.
  - Nash, Eleanor
  - Neely, Henry M.
  - Neider, Charles
  - Neisser, Edith G.
  - Newgass, James
  - Neuman, George C.
  - Neumann, William L.
  - Newberry, Clare Turley
  - Newman, Harold
  - Newmann, William S.
  - Niles, Newton
  - Nicol, Eric
  - Nicols, Claire (White)
  - Nock, Albert Jay
  - Noguchi
  - Nordstrom, Ursula
  - Nordyke, Lewis
  - Norman, Philip
  - Norris, Frank
  - Norton, Lucy
  - Norwich, John Julius
  - Notestein, Wallace
  - Nourse, Alan E.
  - Novak, Michael
  - Nuccio, Sol
  - Nye, Russell Blaine
  - Oakes, John B.
  - Oates, Stephen B.
  - Obenhaus, Dr. Victor
  - Oberth, Hermann
  - Obregon, Mauricio
  - O'Brien, Joseph
  - O'Brien, Kate
  - Ochs, Adolph (Box 333)
  - O'Connar Edwin
  - O'Connor, Jack
  - Osborne, Lloyd
  - Oka, Hideyuki
  - O'Malley, Michael
  - Ormond, Clyde
  - Osofsky, Gilbert
  - Ostow, Mortimer, M. D.
  - Ostrander, Gilman M.
  - Ostrow, Albert
  - Otway, Howard
  - Owen, Janet Curren
  - Pach, Walter
  - Paine, Albert
  - Palatin, Phillip Dr., Ellen C.
  - Philtine
  - Palmer, Stuart
  - Paris, Robert Graham
  - Parker, Harley W.
  - Parks, David
  - Parrish, Anne
  - Pate, Lloyd W.
  - Patterson, Sterling
  - Patteson, Knight
  - Pearlman, Moshe
  - Pearson, Hesketh
  - Peattie, Roderick
  - Pechter, William S.
  - Peck, James L. H.
  - Peeples, Samuel A.
  - Peery, James Robert
  - Peffer, Nathaniel
  - Peltier, Leslie C.
  - Pendray, G. Edward
  - Perlman, Helen Harris
  - Perventsev, Arkady A.
  - Pettit, Paul
  - Preffer, Richard
  - Pfeiffer, John
  - Phillips, John
  - Phillips, T. H.
  - Prince Phillip
  - Picken, Mary Brooks (Box 334)
  - Pickrel, Paul
  - Pierhal, Armand
  - Pilgrem, David
  - Pinkerton, Robert E.
  - Pinto, Oreste
  - Pitcher, Evelyn, Goodenough
  - Plant, Richard
  - Plath, Sylvia
  - Plutzik, Hyam
  - Pomilio, Mario
  - Porter, Elias, H.
  - Porterfield, Nolan
  - Poston, Richard W.
  - Pratt, Fletcher
  - Prescott, Orville
  - Preston, Wheeler
  - Price, Stephen S.
  - Priest, Christopher
  - Priestley, J. B.
  - Prince Phillip Mountbatten
  - Procter, Maurice
  - Prokosch, Federic
  - Prou, Suzanne
  - Provins, Leroy
  - Prudden, Bonnie
  - Pruitt, William O.
  - Pryor, Karen
  - Pudney, John
  - Pugh, Marshall
  - Pulaski, Mary Ann, Dr.
  - Pulitzer Prize Judges - 1941
  - Putnam, Peter
  - Putney, Gladys & Snell
  - Pyle, Howard
  - Queneau, Raymond
  - Quinley, Harold E.
  - Raab, Earl
  - Rabassa, Gregory
  - Radhakrishnan, Sarvepalli, Dr.
  - Radler, D. H.
  - Raisz, Erwin
  - Ralph, Philip
  - Rapoport, Ron
  - Rapport, Samuel
  - Rau, Samtha Rama
  - Raymond, Aron
  - Raymond, Jack
  - Raven, Simon
  - Rawicz
  - Ray, Marie P.
  - Raymond, Louise
  - Redding, J. Saundrus
  - Redgrave, Machael
  - Reed, David (Box 335)
  - Reeden
  - Rees, Goronny
  - Reeves, James
  - Reichmann, Max
  - Reilly, Dr. William J.
  - Reinhardt, Richard
  - Rennie, Ysabel
  - Reston, James
  - Reves, Emery
  - Reynolds, Quentin
  - Rhodin, Eric
  - Rhys, Jean
  - Rice, Elmer
  - Ridgway, Matthew B.
  - Rice, John
  - Rice, F. Philip
  - Rich, Adrienne Cecile
  - Rich, Louise Dickinson
  - Rieff, Philip
  - Rieman, Terry
  - Riessman, Frank
  - Riley, Lt. James C.
  - Ripley, Dillon
  - Rivers, William L.
  - Robeson, Paul
  - Robinson, Edward G.
  - Robinson, Jane
  - Robinson, Paul
  - Robinson, Gerda
  - Rodahl, Kaare
  - Rodman, Selden
  - Roe, Ivan
  - Rogens, Samuel
  - Rohn, Fred H.
  - Rallins, Alice R.
  - Roman, Howard
  - Rombi, Paride
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor
  - Roosevelt, Hall
  - Roosevelt, Kermit
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas
  - Roper, Lanning
  - Rosen, Milton W.
  - Rosenman, Samuel I.
  - Ross, Elaine L.
  - Ross, Ishbel
  - Ross, Mabel
  - Ross, Martin J.
  - Ross, Marvin P.
  - Rossi, Jean Baptiste
  - Rosten, Leo (Box 336)
  - Roth, Sanford
  - Roulston, Marjorie Hills
  - Roy, Jules
  - Rubin, Michael
  - Rubin, Seymour J.
  - Rude, George
  - Rudy, Dr. Willis
  - Rue, Leonard Lee
  - Rugg, Harold
  - Rugh, Dr. Roberts
  - Rushmore, Arthur
  - Ruesch, Hans
  - Russell, William Howard
  - Ryan, Bernard, Jr.
  - Ryan, Leonard Eames
  - Sack, John
  - Sackett, Walter W. Jr. MD
  - St. Denis, Ruth
  - Sagan, Francoise
  - St. Hill, Thomas Nast
  - St. John, Bruce
  - Salsbury, Harrison E.
  - Salsbury, Mrs. Charles B.
  - Salsbury, Dr. Stephen
  - Salter, J. T.
  - Sampson, Anthony
  - Samson, Erin
  - Sanders, Ronald
  - Sandoz, Mari
  - Sanford, Terry
  - Sarratt, Reed
  - Saundby, Sir R.
  - Sauers, Don
  - Sauers, Don & Dedini Eldon
  - Saxton, Alexander
  - Saxton, Eugene F.]
  - Scannell, Francis P.
  - Schellenberg, Walter
  - Schiller, Loe Lund
  - Schneer, Cecil
  - Schiotz, Aksel
  - Schmoe, Floyd
  - Schoenbrun, David
  - Schroeder, Robert E.
  - Schumpeter
  - Schwab, Victor O.
  - Sciascia, Leonardo
  - Searls, Hank
  - Seashore, Stanley E. Ph. D.
  - Segal, Erich
  - Seifert, Mary Harris
  - Selden, George
  - Seles, Floyd
  - Self, Margaret C.
  - Selle, Earl, Albert
  - Selznich, Gertrude
  - Settle, Mary Lee
  - Sexton, Ethol
  - Shaplen, Robert
  - Shaw, Felicity
  - Shaw, Harry
  - Shea, Nancy (Box 337)
  - Vincent Sheean Family
  - Sheehy, Gail
  - Shelton, William R.
  - Shelton, William S.
  - Sheraton, Mimi
  - Sherrill, Robert
  - Sherwood, Hugh C.
  - Sherwood, Robert
  - Shettles, Landrum B.
  - Shriver, Sergeant
  - Shuman, Max
  - Shultz, George P.
  - Sielmann, Heinz
  - Sigel, Eleanor R.
  - Silberman, Charles
  - Silone, Ignazio
  - Silva-Coronel, Paul
  - Simmons, Harry
  - Simon, Herbert A.
  - Simon, Kate
  - Simonds, F. H.
  - Simonson, Lee
  - Simpson, Howard R.
  - Simpson, William
  - Sims, Edward P.
  - Sinclair, Harold
  - Sinclair, Jo.
  - Singer, I. J.
  - Sitwell, Reresby
  - Sitwell, Osbert
  - Ski Magazine, Editors of
  - Skolle, John
  - Slater, Jerome
  - Sloan, Helen Farr
  - Slaymaker, 11, S. R.
  - Slimming, John
  - John Sloan's NY Scene
  - Sloane, Leonard
  - Smalizried, Kathleen Ann
  - Smelser, Marshall
  - Smith, Anna Perle
  - Smith, Betty
  - Smith, Delos Op. (Box 338)
  - Smith, Elmer R.
  - Smith, G. Milton
  - Smith, H. Shirley
  - Smith, Huston
  - Smith, Isabel
  - Smith, Merriman
  - Smith, Philip Hillyer
  - Smith, R. A.
  - Smith, Robert
  - Snodgrass, W. D.
  - Sokol, Erich
  - Sontag, Raymond
  - Sorensen, Thomas C.
  - Spacks, Barry
  - Spaeth, Joe L.
  - Sparks, Dorothy
  - Sprigge, Elizabeth
  - Spring, Howard
  - Springer, E. Laurence
  - Sprunt, Alexander, Jr.
  - Stabler, C. Norman
  - Stafford, William
  - Stahl, Norma
  - Staley, Eugene
  - Stanton, Edwin F.
  - Stapp, Robert
  - Steele, Max
  - Steinberg, Saul
  - Steiner, Stan
  - Steinhacker, Charles
  - Steinzor, Bernard
  - Steirman & Kittler
  - Stepanchev, Stephen
  - Sterling, Claire
  - Stern, Catherine
  - Stern, Edith
  - Stern, Margaret B.
  - Stern, Oto
  - Stern, Richard G.
  - Stevens, Donald
  - Stevenson, Adlai
  - Stevenson, Fanny & Robert Louis
  - Stevenson, Frances
  - Stikker, Dirk
  - Stimpson, George
  - Stimson, Henry L.
  - Stipp, John
  - Stirling, Monica
  - Stocker, Joseph
  - Stolz, Mary
  - Stone, Grace Zaring
  - Storm, Jameson
  - Storm, Jay
  - Stowman, Knud
  - Strabel, Thelma
  - Straley, John A.
  - Stratton, Chalotte K.
  - Strauss-Hupe, Robert
  - Streeter, Edward (Box 339)
  - Streff, John W.
  - Streit, Clarence
  - Stupka, Arthur
  - Stuurman, Edith
  - Sulkin, Sidney
  - Sulzberger, C. L.
  - Summers, Hollis
  - Sumner, G. Lynn
  - Sumner, Sir Ricketts
  - Sulton, Sir Oliver
  - Swan, Lester A.
  - Swing, Raymond
  - Sykes, Christopher
  - Sykes, Egerton
  - Symes, Lillian
  - Symons, Julian
  - Szasz, M. D.
  - Thomas S.
  - Tabrah, Ruth
  - Taft, Philip
  - Tagliabue, John
  - Talbot, Allan R.
  - Talese, Gay
  - Tantri, K'tut
  - Tarcher, Martin
  - Tarkington, Booth
  - Tate, Sylvia
  - Taylor, Deems
  - Taylor, Demetria
  - Taylor, Francis, Henry
  - Taylor, Louis
  - Taylor, Maxwell D.
  - Taylor, Samuel
  - Taylor, Theodore B.
  - Taylor, Wendell
  - Talieff, Haroun
  - Tchelitchew, Pavel
  - Tebbel, John
  - Templeton, Edith
  - Terhune, Albert Payson
  - Terrot, Charles
  - Terry, Walter
  - Tevis, Walter
  - Thaddeus, Janice, Farrar
  - Thakazhi, Sivasankara Pillai